{
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": "05",
      "answer": "faults",
      "question": "Trust no friend without ________, and love a woman, but no angel."
    },
    {
      "id": "06",
      "answer": "healthy",
      "question": "Laughter is by definition _________."
    },
    {
      "id": "07",
      "answer": "fish",
      "question": "If a ______ is the movement of water embodied, given shape, then cat is a diagram and pattern of subtle air."
    },
    {
      "id": "08",
      "answer": "sin",
      "question": "There is only one real ______ and that is to persuade oneself that the second best is anything but second best."
    },
    {
      "id": "09",
      "answer": "mankind",
      "question": "What is a hero without love for ________."
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "answer": "stealing",
      "question": "Borrowing is not much better than begging; just as lending with interest is not much better than __________."
    },
    {
      "id": "Ekvt9_1rk",
      "answer": "learning",
      "question": "That is what ________ is. You suddenly understand something you've understood all your life, but in a new way."
    },
    {
      "id": "tWbnTu-7-",
      "answer": "fools",
      "question": "In university they don't tell you that the greater part of the law is learning to tolerate _______."
    },
    {
      "id": "a1inU96-d",
      "answer": "ANSWER",
      "question": "That is what ________ is. You suddenly understand something you've understood all your life, but in a new way."
    },
    {
      "id": "ZrnWAle8u",
      "answer": "1",
      "question": "1"
    }
  ]
}